export const Kanjis = {
  "name": "Unit 2 Kanjis",
  "questions": [
    {
      en: 'Sun',
      question: 'Write in Hiragana: 日',
      answers: ['にち', 'がつ', 'ひ', 'すい'],
      answer: 'にち',
      img: "images/b1u2/kanji/sun.gif"
    },
    {
      en: 'Moon',
      question: 'Write in Hiragana: 月',
      answers: ['がつ', 'にち', 'すい', 'もく'],
      answer: 'がつ',
      img: "images/b1u2/kanji/moon.gif"
    },
    {
      en: 'Fire',
      question: 'Write in Hiragana: 火',
      answers: ['か', 'にち', 'もく', 'きん'],
      answer: 'か',
      img: "images/b1u2/kanji/fire.gif"
    },
    {
      en: 'Water',
      question: 'Write in Hiragana: 水',
      answers: ['すい', 'にし', 'ひよ', 'いま'],
      answer: 'すい',
      img: "images/b1u2/kanji/water.gif"
    },
    {
      en: 'Tree',
      question: 'Write in Hiragana: 木',
      answers: ['もく', 'こ', 'ほん', 'よう'],
      answer: 'もく',
      img: "images/b1u2/kanji/tree.gif"
    },
    {
      en: 'Gold',
      question: 'Write in Hiragana: お金',
      answers: ['おかね', 'おすい', 'おか', 'おがつ'],
      answer: 'おかね',
      img: "images/b1u2/kanji/gold.gif"
    },
    {
      en: 'Gold',
      question: 'Write in Hiragana: 金',
      answers: ['きん', 'ど', 'いま', 'ひと'],
      answer: 'きん',
      img: "images/b1u2/kanji/gold.gif"
    },
    {
      en: 'Soil',
      question: 'Write in Hiragana: 土',
      answers: ['つち', 'ほん', 'かね', 'ひと'],
      answer: 'つち',
      img: "images/b1u2/kanji/soil.gif"
    },
    {
      en: 'Weekday',
      question: 'Write in Hiragana: 曜日',
      answers: ['ようび',　'ゆうび', 'ひと', 'もく'],
      answer: 'ようび',
      img: "images/b1u2/kanji/weekday.gif"
    },
    {
      en: 'Book',
      question: 'Write in Hiragana: 本',
      answers: ['ほん', 'ようび', 'つち', 'にち'],
      answer: 'ほん',
      img: "images/b1u2/kanji/book.gif"
    },
    {
      en: 'Person',
      question: 'Write in Hiragana: 人',
      answers: ['ひと', 'ほん', 'ようび', 'つち'],
      answer: 'ひと',
      img: "images/b1u2/kanji/person.gif"
    },
    {
      en: 'Now',
      question: 'Write in Hiragana: 今',
      answers: ['いま', 'ようび', 'ほん', 'きん'],
      answer: 'いま',
      img: "images/b1u2/kanji/now.gif"
    },
    {
      en: 'Temple',
      question: 'Write in Hiragana: 寺',
      answers: ['てら', 'ひと', 'きん', 'がつ'],
      answer: 'てら',
      img: "images/b1u2/kanji/temple.gif"
    },
    {
      en: 'Time',
      question: 'Write in Hiragana: 時',
      answers: ['じ', 'てら', 'いま', 'ほん'],
      answer: 'じ',
      img: "images/b1u2/kanji/time.gif"
    },
    {
      en: 'Half',
      question: 'Write in Hiragana: 半',
      answers: ['はん', 'かたな', 'ようび', 'てら'],
      answer: 'はん',
      img: "images/b1u2/kanji/half.gif"
    },
    {
      en: 'Katana',
      question: 'Write in Hiragana: 刀',
      answers: ['かたな', 'じ', 'もく', 'てら'],
      answer: 'かたな',
      img: "images/b1u2/kanji/katana.gif"
    },
    {
      en: 'Minute',
      question: 'Write in Hiragana: 分',
      answers: ['ぷん', 'かたな', 'じ', 'かね'],
      answer: 'ぷん',
      img: "images/b1u2/kanji/minute.gif"
    }
  ]
}